247onlinenetwork.com 2006-07-19

# Privacy Statement provided by 247onlineNetwork

   **Canada:**  
   Alberta  
   British Columbia  
   Manitoba  
   New Brunswick  
   Newfoundland and Labrador  
   Nova Scotia  
   Northwest Territories  
   Nunavut  
   Ontario  
   Prince Edward Island  
   Saskatchewan  
   Yukon  
  
   **USA:**  
   Alaska  
   California  
   Colorado  
   Florida  
   Georgia  
   Hawaii  
   Indiana  
   Louisiana  
   Massachusetts  
   Maine  
   North Carolina  
   New York  
   Pennsylvania  
   Tennessee  
   Texas  
   Utah  
   Virginia  
   Vermont  
   Washington  
   Wisconsin  
   West Virginia  
   Wyoming  
  
   **Dominican Republic:**  
   Puerto Plata  
  
   **Turks & Caicos:**  
   Ambergris Cays  

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
| 

The 247onlineNetwork community website needs you!!!

The 247onlineNetwork provides an excellent opportunity to create a career or a supplemental income with a fun and rewarding job that you control.

With all the tools provided by the 247onlineNetwork, it is easy to generate revenue and best of all, you keep the cash!

Do you: 

  * want to play a role in your municipality?
  * have contacts with members of the local business community?
  * have a sales or journalism background (or want to get one!)?
  * want to control your own hours and income?

If you answered yes to any of the above, then contact the 247onlineNetwork by [CLICKING HERE](http://www.247onlinenetwork.com/contact_client.php?cityid=0&view=input&topic=1) and begin an exciting new career!

|   
|  |   
  
|   
---  
  
**  
  
Privacy Statement**

This privacy statement is applicable to 247onlineNetwork.com and its affiliate sites.

247onlineNetwork

.com does not collect information that personally identifies individuals except when individuals provide such specific information on a voluntary basis. There may be occasions where specific personal information is requested before an individual can utilize the site. For example, information is requested when a client purchases a listing or focus page or someone requests information about other advertising or business programs.

In all such cases, 

247onlineNetwork.com will collect only information that is voluntarily provided by the user and undertakes that such information will be kept strictly confidential. Individual information provided to 247onlineNetwork.com will not be sold or made available to a third party. 247onlineNetwork.com does reserve the right, however, to perform statistical analyses of user behaviour and characteristics, in order to measure interest in and use of the various sections of its sites so as to improve design and navigation and to gather marketing information. Only aggregated data from these analyses, not individual data, will be used for this purpose.

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to you by a number of affiliate programs and clients. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), may be used to serve ads to you. 

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, a third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.   
  
****  
  
**  
Local Business, Services, News & Events Directory**

* * *  
  
|  **Today's Quote**  

**When the eagles are silent, the parrots begin to jabber.  
-|- Sir Winston Churchill  
**  
  
---  
  
Contents © Copyright 2005,2006, 247onlineNetwork, CommonTechnologies. All Rights reserved. Duplication or replication in whole, or in part of the contents of this Web site are strictly prohibited without the express written consent of [247onlineNetwork](http://www.247onlinenetwork.com/contact_client.php?cityid=0&view=input&topic=101).  View our Privacy policy.

* * *

* * *
